Guide to the Montana Legislature (57th: 2001) records 2000-2002
Montana Historical Society Research Center
- Regular Session
  - Senate
    - Senate Journals
      - 71st Legislative Day - 90th Legislative Day, 2001 March 29 - April 22 (Box-folder 31 / 1-2)
  - Miscellany
    - Bill subject index, 2001 (Box-folder 31 / 3)
    - Sponsor list, 2001 (Box-folder 31 / 4)
- Special Session
  - House and Senate Joint Committees
    - Free Conference Committee Minutes
      - HB 2 (re general appropriations act), 2002 August 10 (Box-folder 32 / 1)
  - House Of Representatives
    - House Standing Committee Minutes
      - Appropriations (includes joint hearing with Senate Finance and Claims on July 24), 2002 July 24 - August 10 (Box-folder 32 / 2-13)
      - Business and Labor [see joint hearing with Senate Business and Labor]
      - Federal Relations, Energy, and Telecommunications [see joint hearing with Senate Energy and Telecommunications]
      - Fish, Wildlife, and Parks [see joint hearing with Senate Fish and Game]
      - Judiciary, 2002 August 7-10 (Box-folder 32 / 14-16)
      - Rules (includes joint hearing with Senate Rules on July 26), 2002 July 26 (Box-folder 32 / 17-18)
      - State Administration [see joint hearing with Senate State Administration]
      - Taxation (includes joint hearing with Senate Taxation on July 30), 2002 July 30 - Aug 10 (Box-folder 32 / 19-26)
    - House Bills
      - Bill nos. 1-33, 2002 (Box-folder 32 / 27-30)
    - House Joint Resolutions
      - Bill no. 1, 2002 (Box-folder 32 / 31)
    - House Bill Status Reports
      - 1st Legislative Day - 6th Legislative Day, 2002 July 24 - August 13 (Box-folder 32 / 32)
    - House Journals
      - 1st Legislative Day - 6th Legislative Day, 2002 August 5-10 (Box-folder 32 / 33)
  - Senate
    - Senate Standing Committee Minutes
      - Business and Labor: joint informational hearing with House Business and Labor regarding economic development, 2002 August 5 (Box-folder 32 / 34)
      - Energy and Telecommunications: joint informational hearing with House Federal Relations, Energy, and Telecommunications re energy issues, 2002 August 9 (Box-folder 32 / 35)
      - Fish and Game: joint informational hearing with House Fish, Wildlife and Parks re wolf recovery program, 2002 August 7 (Box-folder 32 / 36)
      - Finance and Claims [see also: House Appropriations], 2002 August 6-10 (Box-folder 32 / 37-41)
      - Judiciary, 2002 August 5-7 (Box-folder 32 / 42-44)
      - Rules [see also: House Rules], 2002 July 26 (Box-folder 32 / 45)
      - State Administration (minutes were not produced for joint informational hearings with House State Administration regarding homeland security, districting and apportionment, and veterans' issues), 2002 August 5-9 (Box-folder 32 / 46-48)
      - Taxation [see also: House Taxation], 2002 July 30 - September 3 (Box-folder 32 / 49-53)
      - Taxation, 2002 August 9-10 (Box-folder 33 / 1-2)
    - Senate Bills
      - Bill nos. 1-33, 2002 (Box-folder 33 / 3)
    - Senate Resolutions
      - Bill nos. 1-4, 2002 (Box-folder 33 / 4)
    - Senate Bill Status Reports
      - 1st Legislative Day - 6th Legislative Day, 2002 August 5 - September 3 (Box-folder 33 / 5)
    - Senate Journals
      - 1st Legislative Day - 6th Legislative Day, 2002 August 5 - September 3 (Box-folder 33 / 6)
- Second Special Session
  - House of Representatives
    - House Standing Committee Minutes
      - Appropriations, 2002 September 13 (Box-folder 33 / 7)
    - House Bills
      - Bill no. 1, 2002 (Box-folder 33 / 8)
    - House Journals
      - 1st Legislative Day, 2002 September 13 (Box-folder 33 / 9)
  - Senate
    - Senate Standing Committee Minutes
      - Finance and Claims, 2002 September 13 (Box-folder 33 / 10)
    - Senate Journals
      - 1st Legislative Day, 2002 September 13 (Box-folder 33 / 11)